why didn't they provide
почему в Донбассе не предоставили
Yanukovych's plane in Donbass He could have flown not
самолёт Януковича Он бы может полетел не
to Russia but to Germany or somewhere
в Россию а в Германию или куда-нибудь
in
там на
Popania Why I'll explain Because
Попанею Почему Я объясню Потому что у
we have a director of Donetsk airport So he
нас директор Донецкого аэропорта так он
was If you know what his
был если ты знаешь знаешь какая его
last name was Yes I'm not interested in that
фамилия была Да мне не интересно это
Tell me why they provided the plane Let's
Скажи почему предоставили самолёт
explain in words Because he was the
Обясним словом Потому что он был
director of Donetsk airport He was
директор донецкого аэропорта был
Turchynov's cousin And that's all
двоюродным братом Турчинова И всё
Turchynov called him to say: "Do not
Турчинов ему позвонил сказать: "Не
provide Yanukovych's plane Do not
предоставлять самолёт Януковича не
give the right to take off"
давать права на вылет"
Oh hello blogger I haven't seen you for a long time Where are you
О привет блогер Давно я тебя не ви Ты
from Where are you from In short, you keep glorifying
откуда Откуда Ты всё короче прославляешь
Bender Yes, I glorify Bandera Glory to
Бендеру Да прославляю Бандеру Слава
Bandera Glory to Stepan Andreevich Bandera
Бандере Слава Степану Андреевичу Бандери
Glory to Bandera And what are you glorifying
слава А ты что прославляешь
I am Vladimir Vladimirovich Putin Come on,
Я Владимира Владимировича Путина Давай
glorify I
прославь
mean Well, glorify
В смысле Ну прославь
And we don't have such stupidity in our heads So do
А мы такой дурости не имеем в голове Тож
you glorify him or not
ты его прославляешь или нет
Oh, for the word Come on You are a competent
Ой уже за слово Давай так Ты ж грамотный
blogger And how do you like it  that's not shameful You'll
блогер И как тебе вот это не стыдно Тебе
have to Yes, you're probably already from Ukraine
же придётся Да ты уже наверное с Украины
Where are you sitting now Tell me In
Где ты сейчас сидишь Вот скажи В
Papuan Guinea
Папуановой Гвинеи
Oh, great The Russians certainly won't get you there They won't
О отлично Там тебя конечно русские не
get you yeah And do you know
достанут Не достанут да А ты знаешь
how many people I read your comments there
сколько вот людей твои комментарии я там
How many people want you I just
читаю сколько людей хотят тебя просто
know I know PolRos wants me
Знаю Знаю ПолРос хочет меня
Well, why are you doing this You're
Ну а зачем ты это делаешь Ты же
inciting national I'm inciting and
разжигаешь национальную Разжигаю да
inciting I'm paid for this by GazDeb and
разжигаю Мне за это платит газдеб и
Europe They pay me money to
Европа Платят бабки мне за то чтобы я
incite hatred towards Russians Because
разжигал ненависть к россиянам Потому
Russia I'll explain Look, this is my job Yes, I don't care
Россия Объясню смотри это моя работа да
about Russia at all But
мне мне вообще всё равно на Россия но
I get paid for this For example, a soldier
мне платят за это деньги Например солдат
from Russia kills people in Ukraine That's
из России убивает людей в Украине это
his job He gets paid for this Yes And
его работа ему платят за это деньги да А
I'm just inciting hatred towards Russians
я просто разжикаю ненависть к россиянам
I get paid for this What will I do
Мне платят за это деньги Что я сделаю
It's just work I get it You're all
Это работа просто работа Я понял Вы все
corrupt Oh, come on Look, you all
продажные Да ну как Смотри все ты тоже
work for money too A Russian soldier
за деньги работаешь Солдат российский за
goes and kills people in Ukraine for money That's
деньги идёт убивает людей в Украине Это
business Let's not get into it Let's not get into it That's what
бизнес Давай без поноса давай без поноса
I need  not interested Tell me please, well, I
Вот мне это неинтересно Скажи пожалуйста
think you're from where From Kyiv
вот ты ну я так думаю ты откуда С Киева
No, I'm from Donetsk
Нет сам родом я из Донецка
Yeah And you were on the Maidan in Kyiv On what On
Ага А на Майдане в Киеве был На каком На
No, not me On No, I was when it was
Нет не я на Нет я когда был
1913-1914 I was still on the
тринадцатый-четырнадцатый год я ещё был
anti-Maidan I was yes, I was in the Party of
на антимайдане Я был да я был в партии
Regions yes, I was a member I headed the
регионов да я был член я возглавлял
Makeyevka city youth council of the
Макеевской городской молоджный совет
party
партии
Seriously
Серьёзно
Ran No need for me Okay, go on Yeah Do you
Бежал Не надо мне Ладно дальше
have normal questions for me or a
Да Нормальные вопросы есть ко мне или
question Come on, you ask I asked you but I'm
вопрос Давай ты задавай Я теб задал но
not interested in it That you were there in the
мне не интересен это Что ты был там в
Party of
партии
Regions Party of Regions head of the
регионов Парти регионов глава
youth department Was was was No
молодёжного отделения Был был был Не
need to prove or show me Let's go
надо мне доказывать и показывать Давай
on like this Uh, let's say you're on the
так дальше Э-э вот ты допустим на
Maidan yeah How did the Maidan end Do you
Майдане да Чем закончился майдан Ты вот
understand or not Maidan
понимаешь или не понимаешь Майдан
ended with the Americans staging a
закончился тем что американцы сделали
coup d'etat in Ukraine
государственный переворот в Украине
And how is it legal or illegal Of course How
И как законно или незаконно Конечно Как
can a coup d'etat be legal There is
государственный переворот может быть
nothing in the constitution about a coup
законно В конституции нет про
d'etat for it to be
государственный переворот чтобы он был
legal American money Have you read the
законным американские деньги Ты ты читал
constitution of Ukraine Of course I told you  I
конституцию Украины Конечно я тебе
'll explain I'm just a person when
объясню Я просто я вообще человек когда
Yanukovych was in power I was in the Party of
при власти был Янукович я был в партии
Regions It was my job When the
региони Это была моя работа Когда
Americans came to power here they put
американцы пришли к власти тут поставили
their puppets in place I went to work for
своих марионеток я перешёл работать на
America Everything is fine Got it Got it
Америку Всё нормально Понял Понял понял
Look at Yanukovych on the day when the
Вот смотри Януковича в день когда вышло
decree was issued to remove Yanukovych and there was the
постановление о снятии Януковича и там
appointment of acting Turchynov You were still in
назначение ИО Турчинова Ты ещё на
Donbass Yes Yes you were still in Donbass And
Донбассе был Да Да ещё на Донбассе был А
what No otherwise it didn't affect you at all as they say
что Не а то тебя вообще как говорится не
And that's already look that was already
коснулось А то это уже смотри это уже
in April I'll
это в апреле месяце уже было Я тебе
explain to you Look how it turns out We in
объясню Смотри как получается Мы на
Donbass we thought until the last that
Донбассе мы до последнего думали что
now Yanukovych would return and say: "I'm the
сейчас Янукович вернётся и скажет: "Я
president, I'm putting things in
президент я навожу
order" But he didn't return But wait
порядок" А он не вернулся А подожди
wait Oh I get it Why didn't he return I do
подожди О я понял А почему не вернулся Я
n't know It seems to me that Russian
не знаю Мне кажется его российские
special services kidnapped him and are holding him in Rostov Got it got it got
спецслужбы выкрали и в Ростове держат
it Awesome Well
Понял понял понял понял Обалденно Ну
in short, like all Ukrainian bloggers you
короче как все украинские блогеры ты
pin everything on Russia Of course I
спираешь всё на Россию Ну конечно Я
look if I'm working for America now
смотри если я сейчас работаю на Америку
of course I'll pin it  to Russia Yes,
конечно я буду спирать на Россию Да
work for whoever you want Although I
работай на кого хочешь Хоть я
understood Platt America and Europe You
понял Платт Америка и Европа Всё
understand everything I get paid I work I
понимаешь Мне платят Я работаю я
stirred up trouble When I was previously in the Party of
разжиганил когда я был раньше в партии
Regions, the Party of Regions paid me
регионов мне платила партия регионов
Lyovochka I don’t care that you’re from the
Лёвочки мне это не интересно что ты с
region that you pay only for money You
региона что ты платишь только за деньги
do this You’re a great guy Please tell me,
это делаешь Да ты вообще молодец Скажи
please, why did
пожалуйста вот пожалуйста почему в
n’t they provide Yanukovych’s plane in Donbass
Донбассе не предоставили самолёт
He could have flown not to
Януковича Он бы может полетел не в
Russia but to Germany or somewhere there
Россию а в Германию или куда-нибудь там
to Popavineya
на Попавинею
Why I’ll explain Because we have a
Почему Я объясню Потому что у нас
director of the Donetsk airport So he
директор ээ Донецкого аэропорта Так он
was if you know what his
был если ты знаешь знаешь какая его
last name was Yes I’m not interested in this You
фамилия была Да мне неинтересно это Ты
tell me why they didn’t provide a plane I’ll
скажи почему не предоставили самолёт
explain because he was the director of the
Объясняю потому что он был директор
Donetsk airport was
Донецкого аэропорта был двоюродным
Turchynov’s cousin And that’s all Turchynov
братом Турчинова И всё Турчинов ему
called him to say: “Do not provide
позвонил сказать: "Не предоставлять
Yanukovych’s plane, do not give the right to
самолёт Януковича не давать права на
take off” That is, who is Turchynov, do you
вылет" То есть а кто такой Турчинов ты
even understand He’s an American
хоть понимаешь Это американский
protégé, you understand The Americans
ставленник понимаешь Американцы
put him in charge And what about him Why did
поставили его И что ему Почему
this
подчинился этот как
brother, as they say, obey there or because he
говорится брат там или потому что он его
cousin He says: "Still
двоюродный брат Он говорит его: "Всё
no" He says: "Now I'll be the boss" You
нет" Он говорит: "Я теперь буду главный"
understand everything, we all know
Всё понимаешь мы всё
what kind of mess you have in your head
какая Что у тебя за каша в голове
So it was real Look, cousin,
Так так было реально Посмотри двоюродная
not everyone knows I've watched too many of your videos
не каждый знает Видиков твоих
Yanukovych's cousin didn't
пересмотрел Двоюродный брат Януковича не
let Turchynov fly
дал Турчинова не дал вылететь Януковичу
out of Donetsk Okay, okay, okay, okay And do you know, let's say,
из Донецка Ладно ладно ладно ладно А ты
how about two people came to
что как там ну два человека пришло на
Ukraine, I think Girkin and Strelkov, and
Украину по-моему Гиркин и Стрелков и
captured the city of Slavyan No, it wasn't like that
захватили город Славян Нет там не так
There was nothing like that Look, they
было Там не так было Смотри это нам
tell us that it was like that
рассказывают что это так ну
for real Yes, there were Donetsk
по-настоящему было да там донецкие
miners, there was a mine named
шахтёры вот была такая шахта имени
Zasyadka Yes, they hid in the mine Yes, they
Засядька да они засели в шахте да они
all were there since 2004, when the first
все с 2004 года когда был первый
orange Maidan took place Yes, they collected weapons,
оранжевый майдан да они собирали оружие
bought them illegally and stored them in the mine
покупали нелегально и складывали в шахте
Yes, on April 12, 1914, they
да 12 апреля четырнадцатого года они
left the mine and headed to the city of
вышли из шахты и направились в город
Slavensk
Славенск
1,488 Shakhtyov You want to say today is the
1.488 шахтёв Ты хочешь сказать сегодня
anniversary of this chi like Yes, yes, yes
прямо юбилей этого чи как Да да да
Today too, yes today is April 12, and
Сегодня тоже да сегодня 12 апреля да и
1.48 people made a march on Slavyansk And
1.48 человек сделали марш на Славянск И
then Girkin arrived They called and
тогда уже приехал Гиркин Они позвонили и
said: "Come" He arrived Wait, wait,
говорит: "Приезжай" Он приехал Подожди
wait And what about Slavyansk not to
подожди подожди А что по Славянска не на
Kyiv I'll explain Because they understood
Киев Объясню Потому что они да понимали
that they wouldn't have enough money to get to
что у них не хватит средств дойти до
Kyiv they'd be stopped And they didn't reach Slavyansk They
Киева их остановят А Славянска не дошли
took it, they had an idea to raise the whole
Взяли у них была идея поднять весь
Donbass What's there, what's so special about this
Донбасс Что там что там такого в этом
Slavyansk Close to the mine, the mine, the ambush, it
Славянске Близко шахта шахта засядька
was 14 km 88 m from Slavyansk That's
было 14 км 88 м от Славянска Это
enough to walk there in 2-3 hours
достаточно чтобы пешим ходом за 2-3 часа
Okay, now wait, wait
дойти Хорошо теперь подожди подожди Вот
I'm also interested Uh, if they marched on
мне ещё интересно Ээ если они по на
Slavyansk, then there was still Ukrainian
Славянск значит там была украинская ещё
power there, this one that sold out Yanukovych And what
власть вот эта продавшая Януковича А в
power was there in Donbass So
Донбассе уже какая власть была Так
Slavyansk is also Donbass Yes, I'm in I'm
Славянск- это тоже Донбасс был Да я в я
not in Donbass Slavyans  this is Donbass In
не в Донбас Славянс это Донбасс В
Donetsk I ask Donetsk Donetsk
Донецке я спрашиваю Донецк Донецк ещё
was still under Ukraine Donetsk there
тогда был под Украиной Донецк там вот
all these Akhmetov held you understand Akhmetov
эти все Ахметов держал понимаешь Ахметов
wanted people said: "Sakhty for Syadko
хотел люди сказали: "Сахты за Сядька
went out: "We took Slavyansk, we'll take
вышли: "Мы взяли Славянск возьмём и
Donetsk too" Akhmetov said: "No, I'm the
Донец" Ахметов сказал: "Нет я тут
main one in Donbass" They told him:
главный на Донбассе" Они ему сказали:
"No, look who Akhmetov is Who is he What do you
"Нет смотри кто такой Ахметов Кто такой
mean who is he?" He was the head of Donetsk
В смысле кто такой?" Он глава Донецка
He held everything in his hands From
был Он всё держал всё в его руках От
Donbass Avina what are you with you that there
Донбасс Авины что ты у вас что там
was generally anarchy there Akhmetov held
вообще безвластие было Ахметов держал
Donbass too Yes Akhmet Donbass is
Донбасс тож Да Ахмет Донбасс - это
Akhmetov Akhmetov is Donbass Everyone
Ахметов Ахметов - это Донбасс Каждый
knows in Russia
знает в России
Well, how did you change your views
Ну и как ты поменял свои взгляды
Everything is simple The government has changed
Всё просто Поменялась власть Поменялась
I have always been for the government I am a simple person I am
я за власть всегда Я простой человек Я
not interested in politics The government Yanukovych
политикой не интересуюсь Власть Янукович
I was with the party the government You have an illegal
Я был с партию власть У тебя незаконная
government Look I don't know I see they are the
власть Смотри я не знаю Я смотрю они
president are they legal or illegal I
президент они законны или незаконные я
don't understand  I don't understand
не разбираюсь Я не разбираюсь в
constitutions in politics Understood understood understood understood understood
конституциях в политике Поня понял понял
You are a hutskraynik, you could
понял понял понял Ты хатаскрайник можно
say Yes there is Yes I am a hutskray There is
сказать Да есть Да я хата скрай Есть
power I work with it It pays and it
власть я с ней работаю Платит она
works The whites have come Well yes yes I will
работает Белые пришли Ну да да
come for the people you understand I am not for the people
прилю для людей понимаешь Я не для людей
you are stirring up a national for the people here I am stirring up
ты разжигаешь здесь национальную для
for the people Traitor You are a traitor you
людей Я разжигаю для людей Предатель Ты
understand Betrayed It was Yanukovych who
предатель понимаеш Предала Это Янукович
betrayed me Yanukovych betrayed me and the people of
предал меня Янукович меня предал и народ
Donbass Wait okay Okay Yanukovych
Донбасса Подожди ладно Ладно Янукович
betrayed you Danukovich was
тебя предал Дануковича два раза
assassinated twice while he was on his way to Kharkov
покушение было пока он ехал в Харьков
Because I voted for him I carried
Потому что я голосовал за него Я за него
ballots for him in batches you understand Oh here I
бюллетени пачками таскал понимаешь О тут
voted What is this I voted for Why did
голосовал Что это голосовал Что ж ты его
n't you defend him How can I defend him I'm
не защищал Как я могу защитить Я
not interested in politics What do I have He
политикой не интересуюсь У меня что есть
had the SBU All that they didn't
У него было СБУ Всё что они его не
defend him Come on while you are a hutskray What
защитили Давай пока ты хата край Что Та
Not you are
не ты
running away Grandpa's brain was blown That's how it
убегаешь Деду взорвали мозг Вот так с
should be with this Yes yes yes America yes Donbass
этим и нужно Да да да Америка да Донбасс
yes like  subscribe comment This was a bomb
да лайк подписка комент Це был бомбезный
video Subscribe to my Telegram right
ролик Підпишись на мій Telegram прям
now Axis Vin And the
зараз Ось він А
priest is even more and more important YouTube is
попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
pushing us through the karger into a new ban And the
заганяе нас через каргер в тньовий бан І
video is not shown to people
дуже багато відео не показуется людям
at all times Information about the stream is not shown
вчасно не показуется інформація про
That’s why we need to be small
стрими Тому для того щоб ми мали
operational link subscribe directly
оперативный зв'язок підпишиться прямо
now And the pop there in telegram okmdeo is
зараз А попик там в телеграмі окмдео ще
also useful and useful information and we are
теж цікава и корисна інформація и мы
obliged to you to provide a permanent
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational link Regardless of that, I
оперативный зв'язок Незалежно від того
will show you about this YouTube Glory to
чи покаже вам про цей YouTube Слава
Ukraine  Subscribe
Україні Підпишись